

#### **Profile**

I am a self-learner Front-end Developer who is always exposed to new technologies, eager to learn and develop my skills. I have 5+ years of experience varied between working as a part of a team on a School Website and as a Freelancer who is responsible to manage the whole process of development. I started my career as an English Teacher and decided to make a career shift and this is because of my passion for Technology.

## **Key Accomplished**

- · Created a full UI school website
- Defined an automated process to facilitate School/Parents communications
- Successfully made good relationship with customers of different cultures
- Scheduled a learning path for myself till I became a confident frontend developer
- · Published a series of English learning books as a foreign language
- Organized a large event for 50+ School members' to present my books

# **Employment History**

Web Developer, Freelancing, Zürich

MAY, 2018 - PRESENT

- Debug/Implement elements according to clients' requirements. Besides, building websites using latest technology: React Hooks/React-Bootrap..etc.
- Dealing with and selling elements to different customers with different cultures.

## Sales specialist, für 2 Franken Shop, Zürich

JUNE, 2021 - DECEMBER, 2021

- Facilitates sales, greet customers and offer them assistance.
- Processes payments, help and advise customers.

# Frontend Developer, Thebes School, Cairo

SEPTEMBER, 2013 - May, 2017

- Create the UI for the school website including HTML, CSS, JS and JQuery.
- Responsible for implementing all HTTP REQUESTS needed for students marks, login, messages, school notifications... etc.

#### **Details**

Haldenstrasse 30, 8134 daliagadelhak@gmail.com +41787271715

# Technical Skills

HTML5/PSD TO HTML5

CSS3/SCSS

RESPONSIVE-WEB-DESIGN/BOOTSTRAP4

JAVASCRIPT/ES6/JQUERY

**REACT/REACT-HOOKS** 

NPM/YARN PACKAGE MANAGER

**CONSUMING RESTFUL-APIS** 

**BROWSER DEVELOPER TOOLS** 

**VISUAL STUDIO CODE/ SEMENTIC CODE** 

**GIT/GITHUB** 

**UNIT TESTING: JEST/ENZYME** 

**REDUX** 

**NODE JS/MONGO DB** 

**UI PRINCIPLES** 

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP/ILLUSTRATOR

## Soft Skills

TEAM WORK/ANALYTICAL THINKING

**CONVINCING CLIENTS** 

**WILLING TO LEARN NEW TECHNOLOGIES** 

### Owner/Manager, M&M Nursery, Cairo

SEPTEMBER, 2012 - SEPTEMBER, 2015

Open and manage a nursery for children till school entry

#### Executive Secretary, Memphis School, Cairo

JANUARY, 2011 - SEPTEMBER, 2013

- Manage an active calendar for the school manager.
- Handle and prioritize all outgoing or incoming correspondence.

# Writer/English Supervisor, "Mr. Mack" Supplementary Books, Cairo AUGUST, 2005 - JANUARY, 2011

- Publish my series of English books/Supervise the teachers' work.
- Organize a training course for the teachers twice a year.

## **Education**

Bachelor Degree, Faculty of Languages, Ain Shams University, Cairo SEPTEMBER, 2001 - MAY, 2005

#### **Courses**

Javascript/React/Bootsrtap4/Wordpress/Jest, Udemy FEBRUARY, 2013 - PRESENT

Languages ENGLISH	
ARABIC	
GERMAN	
FRENCH	

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Understand the concepts of Scrum/Agile Methodology
- Available work permit
- My Portfolio Link: https://daliagadelhak.github.io/